<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Android Guide</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="help">The terminology section of this app will allow the user to enter the name of a term and to view the defination. The websites section shows the user
    12 websites, that are useful for developing android apps.</string>
    <string name="help_description">The Terminology section contains definations from Labs 1 and 2. The websites section contains a list of 12
    websites relating android programming.</string>
    <string name="about_name">Name: Nitish Bajaj</string>
    <string name="about_program">Program: Computer Programming</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="title_activity_terminology">Terminology</string>
    <string name="title_activity_websites">Websites</string>
    <string name="websites_description">The websites section of this app shows you with 12 options that are links to pages that will help you develop apps for android.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_help">Help</string>
    <string name="title_activity_about">about</string>

    <string-array name="name">
        <item>adb</item>
        <item>emulator</item>
        <item>android</item>
        <item>screenshot2</item>
        <item>gradle</item>
        <item>pm</item>
        <item>lint</item>
        <item>src/main</item>
        <item>build/outputs</item>
        <item>res/layout</item>
        <item>res/values</item>
        <item>project</item>
        <item>panel</item>
        <item>toolbar</item>
        <item>status bar</item>
        <item>preview pane</item>
        <item>android pane</item>
        <item>project explorer</item>
        <item>.idea folder</item>
        <item>intellisense</item>
        <item>module">-</item>
        <item>live layout</item>
        <item>init</item>
        <item>commit</item>
        <item>push</item>
        <item>add</item>
        <item>pull</item>
        <item>branch</item>
        <item>clone</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="def">
        <item>- adb allows us to connect/interact or go in to our AVD. Commands such as "adb shell"</item>
        <item>- Using the emulator command, we can run the AVD through command line.</item>
        <item>- We used android list avd to list our android virtual devices.</item>
        <item>- This allows us to take screenshot inside the emulator. This way we can take screenshots of whats happening inside the emulator rather than, print screen and then cropping our image.</item>
        <item>- Gradle is the build tool, it allows us to build our project.</item>
        <item>- pm command with uninstall alllows us to remove the app.</item>
        <item>- This is where all the errors and warnings are stored/written</item>
        <item>- By using tree command, it looks like main is where all the files and folders go, in a project. It\'s where you start placing files.</item>
        <item>- This directory contains lint files, and APK\'s, like the one we ran in part C4.</item>
        <item>- Contains the layout files. How you want the text, images or items in your programs to look on the emulator when they get displayed.</item>
        <item>- You can declare string variables and store or assign them some words. We created a file called "strings.xml" and created a variable called "app_name" and gave it the value "Android Gradle" which got printed in our emulator when we ran our hello world/seneca app.</item>
        <item>- A project is where your app is stored, each project contains one app, but multiple files. Project name is the same as your app name</item>
        <item>- An area or a section which contains tools and options.</item>
        <item>- Gives us a quick selection to tools. There are a selection of tools outside in the main window such as SDK manager, emulator menu, run and much more.</item>
        <item>- the bar that appears at the top of your screen/device. Above the "Hello World" string.</item>
        <item>- It is a panel that is displayed in the middle of your project with your vm, that shows your project and the changes you make to it as you go.</item>
        <item>- Let\'s you use features such as taking a screenshot within your vm, system information and give you information about your project and files as you work on it, whether if something failed or not.</item>
        <item>- Lists all the recent projects that you worked on.</item>
        <item>- The .idea directory contains a set of configuration files.</item>
        <item>- It\'s a feature that allows the user to speed up the process of coding by reducing syntax errors.</item>
        <item>-</item>
        <item>- Live Layout means you can view your work/code as you go in the preview pane.</item>
        <item>- Create an empty Git repository or reinitialize an existing one.</item>
        <item>- This allows you to record the changes to your local respository.</item>
        <item>- This allows you to update the remote repository with the local changes.</item>
        <item>- Add file contents to the index.</item>
        <item>- Fetch from and integrate with another repository or a local branch.</item>
        <item>- List, create, or delete branches.</item>
        <item>- Clone a repository into a new directory.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="website">
        <item>Android Studio</item>
        <item>Seneca - MAP524</item>
        <item>The New Boston</item>
        <item>Vogella</item>
        <item>Technotalkative</item>
        <item>Bootcamp Series</item>
        <item>Lynda.com</item>
        <item>Team Treehouse</item>
        <item>Android App Development Google+ Tutorials</item>
        <item>Mobile Tuts+</item>
        <item>Udacity</item>
        <item>Androidhive</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="urls">
        <item>http://developer.android.com/tools/studio/index.html</item>
        <item>https://scs.senecac.on.ca/~john.selmys/subjects/map524-151/</item>
        <item>https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PL6gx4Cwl9DGBsvRxJJOzG4r4k_zLKrnxl</item>
        <item>http://www.vogella.com/tutorials/android.html</item>
        <item>http://www.technotalkative.com/android/</item>
        <item>https://thenewcircle.com/s/post/1017/android_bootcamp_series_2012_video_tutorial</item>
        <item>http://www.lynda.com/Android-training-tutorials/947-0.html</item>
        <item>http://teamtreehouse.com/?utm_source=shareasale&amp;utm_medium=affiliate&amp;utm_campaign=shareasale-aff-program&amp;utm_content=homepage-link&amp;cid=1086&amp;SSAID=871071</item>
        <item>https://plus.google.com/+KevinDarty/posts/Qex6Ae6zhZW</item>
        <item>http://code.tutsplus.com/categories/android</item>
        <item>https://www.udacity.com/course/ud853</item>
        <item>http://www.androidhive.info/</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="title_activity_browser">browser</string>

</resources>